Zack, Arnold Arbitration Files 5512
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Arnold Zack Arbitration Files
1956-1973
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Zack, Arnold
5512
23 cubic feet
23 linear ft.
Arbitration awards, decisions, correspondence, papers.
Consists of over one thousand arbitration awards, primarily in the utilities, rubber, leather, transportation, retail food, steel, publishing, and construction industries. Also public employment awards for educational, postal, fire and police agencies.
3834134
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 11, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 09, 2015
Biographical / Historical
Lawyer, arbitrator, and government official; LLB Yale, 1956, MBA Harvard, 1961, MA Harvard, 1963.
Arnold Marshall Zack is an arbitrator and mediator. Beginning his labor career as a part-time election examiner for the National Labor Relations Board and as a case analyst for the U.S. Wage Stabilization Board (1950-1953), he was also a lecturer in labor economics at Simmons College, Northeastern University (1957-1963); an assistant to Saul Wallen, arbitrator, (1956-1960); director of the Labor-Management Institute of the American Academy of Arbitrators (1966-1968); and has served in various labor-related international posts for the United States government.
Other governmental service includes membership on panels for the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, the Massachusetts Public Employment Relations Board, the New York State Public Employment Relations Board, The New Jersey Public Employment Relations Board, The New York City Office of Collective Bargaining, and The National Mediation Board. Zack is also a panel member of the American Arbitration Association, and has served as the permanent arbitrator for a number of major corporations and unions and for the State of New York and the U.S. Postal Service.
Scope and Contents
Awards include Associated Grocers of New England vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America (IBT)(1973, 1977) on issues of safety, absenteeism, work rules, work assignment, holidays, vacation, discipline, and dismissal; Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company vs. General Warehousemen's Union (IBT), Amalgamated Food Workers, and Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union of America (1971-1973) on issues of employee theft, hours of work, and protective clothing; B.F. Goodrich Company vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers (URW)(1968-1972) on issues of absenteeism, union activity, wage differential, production standards, fringe benefits, disability, suspension, overtime, reinstatement, funeral leave, pension, dismissal, scheduling, personal leave, preferential hiring, seniority, clothing allowance, violence, wage adjustments, workweek, medical benefits, negligence, insubordination, position classification, position description, work injury, workers' compensation, severance pay, and plant shutdown; and Baltimore County, Md. Board of Education vs. Teachers' Association of Baltimore (1971-1977) on issues of management rights, job evaluation, downgrading, substitution, staffing, transfer, job requirements, educational expenditures, collective negotiations, position description, personal leave, seniority, and job requirements.
Other cases include Bangor and Aroostook Railroad Company vs. Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, and United Transportation Union (UTU)(1969-1973) on issues of work assignment, shift differential, violence, negligence, wages, overtime, hours of work, and "deadheading"; Boston and Maine Railway Corporation vs. Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (1964- 1968) on issues of labor dispute settlement and work assignment; British Overseas Airway Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM)(1967-1974) on issues of promotion and overtime; and Canadian Pacific Railroad vs. United Transportation Union (1970) on issues of labor dispute settlements, hours of work, scheduling, union jurisdiction, management rights, and wages.
Other cases include Falmouth, Mass. School Committee vs. Falmouth Educators' Association (1969-1973, 1975) on issues of work assignment, collective negotiations, wages and staffing; First National Stores vs. Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of America, and Foodstore and Allied Workers (1969-1973) on issues of work assignment, wages, dismissal, negligence, employee theft, store closing, and seniority; General Products Corporation vs. International Chemical Workers Union (1964-1969) on the issue of wages; General Tire and Rubber Company vs. URW (1961-1974) on issues of scheduling, work assignment, wages and disability insurance; John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Company vs. Insurance Workers International Union (1970, 1976-1978) on issues of wildcat strike, job performance and management rights; and Jones and Lamson Machine Company vs. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (1955-1964) on issues of corruption, staffing, and union activity.
Other cases include Lakeland, N.Y. Board of Education vs. Lakeland Federation of Teachers (1969-1972) on issues of wages and job requirement; Leesona Corporation vs. IAM (1967-1974) on issues of non-union workers, work assignment, seniority, and security check; Long Island Railroad vs. UTU (1973-1974) on issues of grievance procedure, work assignment, insubordination, and discipline; Marine Colloids Company vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union (1968) on issues of overtime and alcoholism; Maine Central Railroad Company (Portland Terminal) vs. UTU and Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (1973) on issues of seniority, tardiness, negligence, work assignment, dismissal, discipline, grievance procedure, and work rules; Massachusetts Institute of Technology vs. Massachusetts Institute of Technology Research and Development and Technical Employees' Union, and Building Service Employees' International Union (1971-1976) on issues of absenteeism, work assignment, tardiness, seniority, layoff, and staffing; and Mobil Oil Corporation vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers' International Union (OCAW)(1969-1973, 1978) on issues of shop steward and vacations.
Other awards include Nanuet, N.Y. Public Schools vs. Nanuet Teachers' Association (1968-1970) on issues of health insurance and overtime; National Railroad Adjustment Board (Third Division) (1960-1964) on issues of wages, seniority, overtime, work assignment, non-union workers, job performance, fringe benefits and holidays; Northwest Orient Airlines vs. Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, International Air Line Pilots Association, and IBT (1971-1977) on issues of position classification, benefits, wages, discipline, work requirement, overtime, physical capacity, rest period, job performance, work assignment, travel allowance, staffing, seniority, residence requirement, tardiness, absenteeism, non-union workers, and "deadheading"; Sun Oil Company of Pennsylvania vs. OCAW (1974-1975) on issues of staffing, seniority, layoffs, protective clothing, and grievance procedures; Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), and Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority Sergeants' and Lieutenants' Benevolent Association (1969, 1975) on issues of wages and union jurisdiction.
Other awards include United States Postal Service (Connecticut, Massachusetts, New York, New Jersey, Ohio, New Hampshire, and Maine) vs. National Association of Letter Carriers and American Postal Workers Union (1975-1977) on issues of insubordination, collective agreement, violence, layoff, criminal record, alcohol abuse, job requirement, drug abuse, negligence, job performance, disability, employee theft, tardiness, dismissal, master agreement, absenteeism, and discipline; Weyerhaeuser Company (Paper Division) vs. International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers and United Papermakers and Paperworkers (1970) on issues of hours of work, benefits, contracting out and scheduling; and Yale University vs. Federation of University Employees (1973-1977) on issues of overtime, contracting out, backpay, wages, and position classification. Numerous other case files on routine arbitrations included.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5281: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 5551: Arnold M. Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5620: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5659: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5727: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files
Absenteeism -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Alcohol abuse -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Airlines -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Chemical industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- College employees -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Education -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Electric industries -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Electronic industries -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Gas companies -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Grocery trade -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Insurance companies -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Leather industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Machine industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Metal-workers -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Motor bus lines -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Municipal employees -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Paper industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Petroleum industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Plastics industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Postal service -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Railroads -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Rubber industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Social workers -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Teachers -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Cases; Industrial arbitrators; Drug abuse -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Employee fringe benefits -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Employees, Dismissal of -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Employees, Training of -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Grievance procedures -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Industrial safety -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Job descriptions -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Job vacancies -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Labor discipline -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Labor productivity -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Layoffs -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Management rights -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Misconduct -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Vacations, Employee -- Law and legislation -- United States; Plant shutdowns -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Position classification -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Retirement -- Law and legislation -- United States; Seniority, Employee -- Law and legislation -- United States; Strikes and lockouts -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Work assignments -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Employee rules -- United States; Zack, Arnold.; AFSCME; Amalgamated Food Workers of America; Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America; American Postal Workers Union; Associated Grocers of New England; B.F. Goodrich Company.; Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America; Baltimore County (Md.). Board of Education; Bangor and Aroostook Railroad; Boston and Maine Railroad; British Overseas Airways Corporation; Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.); Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen; Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes; Building Service Employees' International Union; Canadian Pacific Railroad; Falmouth (Mass.). School Committee; Falmouth Educators' Association (Falmouth, Mass.); Federation of University Employees; First National Stores, Inc.; Foodstore and Allied Workers; General Products Corporation; General Tire and Rubber Company; Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company; Insurance Workers' International Union; International Air Line Pilots Association; International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers; International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America; International Chemical Workers Union (1944- ); John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Company; Jones and Lamson Machine Company; Lakeland (N.Y.). Board of Education; Lakeland Federation of Teachers (N.Y.); Leesona Corporation; Long Island Railroad Company; Maine Central Railroad Company; Massachusetts Institute of Technology Research and Development and Technical Employees Union; Massachusetts Institute of Technology.; Mobil Oil Corporation; Nanuet Public Schools; Nanuet Teachers' Association; National Association of Letter Carriers of the United States of America; Northwest Airlines; Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union; Sun Oil Company of Pennsylvania; Teachers' Association of Baltimore; Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority; United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America; United Papermakers and Paperworkers; United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers; United States Postal Service.; United States. National Railroad Adjustment Board; United Transportation Union; Weyerhaeuser Company; Yale University.
3834134
- A & P - Atlantic Gummed Paper. (Box 1)
  - Atlantic Gummed Paper Corp. and U.P.U. Local 292 A70-1615, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Associated "Y" and Local 1707 C.S.A.E.U. A70-710, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Armstrong Cork Company and U.R.W.A., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Arlington, VA. School Bd. And Education Assoc., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Town of Arlington and AFSCME, Local 680, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Arlington VA. School Bd. And Bd. Of Ed. Non-Economic Issues, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Anne Arundel Cty. Md. Ed. Assoc. and Ed. Leaders, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Official Products Division, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Kitchen Foods, Inc. -and- IAMAW, Lodge 1198 72A/10557, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - AM. Fed. Gov't. Emp. And Fed. Of Nat. Representatives, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Elastimold Div. of Amerace Esna Corp., 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Alexander's Markets, Inc. -and- Local 372, Retail Store Employees 72A 9841 F.M.C.S., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Compagnie Nationale Air France I.A.M. & A.W.S. / SBA 65-2, 1962-1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Air France and I.A.M. SBA 71-22, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Ainslie Corporation and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers etc. Case L-24764 Bosd L-75-59, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Adams County, Colo. School Dist. #12 and- Dist. #12 Educ. Assoc., 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Adams County School Dist. 14 -and Classroom Teachers Assoc., 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Acme Markets, Inc. and Warehouse Employees Local 169, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Acme Markets, Inc. Teamsters, Local 169, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - A.S. Abell Company and Wash. -Balt. Newspaper Guild, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - A & P Inc. and Amalg. Food Workers Local 10, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - A & P (Gr. Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co) & Gen. Warehouseman's Un., Local 852, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- B.F. Goodrich. (Box 2)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Clarksville, Tenn. And U.R.W.A. 194, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Fort Wayne and U.R.W.A. 715, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Fort Wayne and U.R.W.A. 715, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Fort Wayne, Ind. And U.R.W.A. 715, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Akron, Ohio and U.R.W.A., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Miami, Oklahoma and U.R.W.A. 318, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Miami, Oklahoma and U.R.W.A. 318, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Miami, Oklahoma and U.R.W.A. 318, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Riverside, New Jersey and U.R.W.A. Local 434, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co Riverside N.J., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Akron, Ohio and U.R.W.A. 5, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Akron, Ohio and U.R.W.A. 5, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Oaks, Pa. and U.R.W.A. Local 281, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Miami, Oklahoma and U.R.W.A. 318, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Clarksville Tenn. And U.R.W.A. Local 194, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Akron, Ohio and U.R.W.A. Local 5, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Akron, Ohio and U.R.W.A. Local 5, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Oaks, Pa. and U.R.W.A. 281, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Oaks, Pa. and U.R.W.A. 281, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Oaks, Pa. and U.R.W.A. 281, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Oaks, Pa. and U.R.W.A. 281, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Oaks, Pa. and U.R.W.A. 281, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Fort Wayne Indiana. and U.R.W.A. Local 715, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Oaks, Pa. and U.R.W.A. Local 281, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - B.,F. Goodrich Company Oaks, Pa. and U.R.W.A. 281, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Oaks, Pa. and U.R.W.A. 281, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Marion, Ohio U.R.W.A. Local 241, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Oaks, Pa. and U.R.W.A. Local 281, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - B.f. Goodrich Company Oaks, Pa. and U.R.W.A. Local 281, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Oaks Pa. and U.R.W.A. Local 281, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Akron, Ohio and U.R.W.A. Local 5, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Akron Ohio and U.R.W.A. Local 5, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Akron, Ohio and U.R.W.A. Local 5, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Miami, Oklahoma and U.R.W.A. 318 N-24, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Miami, Oklahoma and U.R.W.A. Local 318, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Los Angeles, California and U.R.W.A. Local 43, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Miami, Oklahoma and U.R.W.A. 318, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Akron, Ohio and U.R.W.A. Local 5, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company and U.R.W.A. No. 5, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company and U.R.W.A. No. 5, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company and U.R.W.A. No. 5, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company and U.R.W.A. No. 5, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Los Angeles, California and U.R.W.A. Local 43, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - B.F> Goodrich Company Clarksville, Tenn. And U.R.W.A. 194, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Clarksville, Tenn. And U.R.W.A. Local 194, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Clarksville, Tenn. And U.R.W.A. Local 194, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Clarksville Tenn. And U.R.W.A. Local 194, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Clarksville Tenn. And U.R.W.A. Local 194, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Clarksville, Tenn. And U.R.W.A. Local 194, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Oaks, Pa. and U.R.W.A. Local 281, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Fort Wayne, Ind. And U.R.W.A. Local 715, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Oaks, Pa. and U.R.W.A. Local 281, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Miami, Oklahoma and U.R.W.A. Local 318, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Akron, Ohio and U.R.W.A. Local 5, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Akron, Ohio and U.R.W.A. Local 5, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Akron, Ohio and U.R.W.A. Local 5, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Akron, Ohio and U.R.W.A. Local 5, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Akron, Ohio and U.R.W.A. Local 5, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Akron, Ohio and U.R.W.A. Local 5, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Oaks Pa. and U.R.W.A. 281, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- B.F. Goodrich - Bent Bros.. (Box 3)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Akron, Ohio and U.R.W.A. Local 5, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Akron, Ohio and U.R.W.A. Local 5, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Oaks, Pa. and U.R.W.A. 281, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Miami, Oklahoma and U.R.W.A. Local 318, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Oaks, Pa. and U.R.W.A. 281, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Oaks, Pa. and U.R.W.A. Local 281, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Clarksville, Tenn. And U.R.W.A. Local 194, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Fort Wayne, Ind. And U.R.W.A. Local 715, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - B.F. Goodrich Company Los Angeles, Calif. And U.R.W.A. Local 43, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Oaks, Pa. and U.R.W.A. Local 281, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Oaks, Pa. and U.R.W.A. Local 281, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. and U.R.W.A. Local 281, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - B.F> Goodrich Co. Riverside, N.J. and U.R.W.A. Local 434, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - B.F> Goodrich Co. Riverside, N.J. (in Akron) and U.R.W.A. Local 434, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - B.F. Goodrich Co. Miami and U.R.W.A. Local 318, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - B.F. Goodrich (Fort Wayne Ind.) & Local 715, U.R.W., 1972 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Baltimore County, Md. Bd. Of Educ. -and- Teachers Assoc., 1972 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Baltimore County Public Schools, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Baltimore Cty. Bd. Ed. And M. Wojtulewicz TABCO, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Baltimore County Public Schools, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Baltimore Cty Bd. Of Ed. And TABCO, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bangor & Aroostook R.R. and U.T.U. Public Law Board 360 #1, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bangor & Aroostook R.R. and U.T.U. Public Law Board 360 #2, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Bangor & Aroostook R.R. and U.T.U. Public Law Board 360 #3, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Bangor & Aroostook R.R. and U.T.U. Public Law Board 360 #4, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Bangor & Aroostook R.R. and U.T.U. P.L.B. 641, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Bangor & Aroostook R.R. and U.T.U. P.L.B. 641 #2, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Bangor & Aroostook R.R. and U.T.U. P.L.B. 641 #3, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Barre Vt. Granite Assoc. and Granite Cutters Int. Assoc., 1971 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Bemis Company and Pulp, Sulphite & Papermill Workers, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - S. Bent & Bros. and U.F.W. Local 154, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Bisson Inc. - Buffalo Bd. of Ed.. (Box 4)
  - Lucien Bisson, Inc. and Teamsters Local 340, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - BLH Electronics and I.A.M. District Lodge 38, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bliss-Portland Company and I.A.M., 1969 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Borden, Inc. -and- ICWU, Local 553, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Borden Chemical Co. and Int. Chem. Wkrs. Local 533, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 5)